Never look back. Never look forward.
Redeeming Love is a romance, drama, western film directed by D.J. Caruso.
A young couple's relationship clashes with the harsh
realities of the California Gold Rush of 1850.
Angel, experiencing love for the first time and facing demons
unsurmountable, runs from the new life she doesn't believe she deserves.
When Michael sets out to find her, Angel discovers that she
indeed has the power to choose the life she wants.
Angel, played by Abigail Cowen.
Michael, played by Tom Lewis.
Duke, played by Eric Dane.
Duchess, played by Famke Janssen.
Paul, played by Logan Marshall-Green.
Mae, played by Nina Dobrev.
Redeeming Love is a 2022 American Christian
Western romance film directed by D.J.
Caruso, who co-wrote the screenplay with Francine Rivers.
The film is based on Rivers' 1991 novel of the same name, which was based on the Biblical story
of Hosea, and is set in the American Old West during the California Gold Rush.
It stars Abigail Cowen, Tom Lewis and Logan Marshall-Green.
The film was co-produced by Pinnacle Peak Pictures, Mission Pictures International,
and Nthibah Pictures, and was filmed in Cape Town, South Africa.
It was theatrically released by Universal Pictures on January 21, 2022, and received
generally negative reviews from critics but was well-received by audiences.
Redeeming Love was nominated for the GMA Dove Award for Inspirational
Film/Series of the Year at the 2022 GMA Dove Awards.
The film explores themes of pedophilia, child abuse,
california, rape, based on novel or book.
The tone is emotional and mind_bending.